Thank you for watching!
I'm fired up.
Yes, good evening, everyone.
Good evening.
The morning chimes have sounded. We, the
We are the private art school.
Today's program is led by me.
Attendance number 12, Yamanashiko Nakayama.
Please do me a favor.
Okay, then.
There is one more.
Attendance number 15, Nanoko Kazami.
Please give her my best regards.
Is this the first time you two have met today?
It's not the first time? It's my first time too.
We always do the showroom with three people, don't we?
Sometimes there were four of us, but this is the first time for two of us.
This is the first time for the two of us.
It's my first time.
I would like to change.
If something happens a little bit with this, I think we'll have three people next time.
Please point me out at that time.
Yes, please.
Yes, let's begin.
Snake in the middle.
A delightful, ho-hum showroom.
Yay.
Today we have the 54th
Snake in the Middle's Delightful and Fufu Showroom.
Thank you for visiting our showroom.
The Snake in the Middle's Delightful and Fufufu Showroom is a sisterhood of ours.
Our little sister
This is the sister show of Ucuka's showroom.
Yes.
Bichu Showroom's original avatar is here today and again this time, isn't it?
Yes, we have a lot of them. Thank you very much.
You can get an original avatar by registering at the showroom and giving a free or paid gift.
We want to fill this place up, don't we? I'd love to fill this place with avatars.
Please fill it with cute avatars.
Please be a part of it. Please do so.
Then it's photo time again, but this time, please click on the Twitter symbol at the bottom of the screen to spread the word about this distribution on Twitter.
So, it's time to spread the word. I'm going to tweet a notice on Twitter now so that as many people as possible can see this distribution.
Please retweet.
Thank you very much.
Please spread the word.
Thank you for coming to play now.
Can you recognize Mr. Nasunakanishi?
Something happened yesterday.
I'm fine now.
Were you easy to find? Until now?
No, it would be very rude if I made a mistake when I suddenly had to say something.
I would say, "This is Mr. Nasu," or "Mr. Nasu Nakanishi," depending on where I was sitting each time.
I was allowed to play the radio every day.
I was doing it with Mr. Nasu-Nakanishi at that time.
At first, I knew which was which.
The one that looks like Mr. Nasu is Mr. Nakanishi, right?
That's right.
That's how I learned.
That's how I learned it.
I learned it yesterday, and I'll do my best to say it without vomiting.
When I looked at Twitter, I saw that this one is Mr. Nasu on the right and so on.
I thought it was interesting.
I was like, "I'm Cocona.
I got a little carried away with Twitter.
Okay, so today, let's do this.
Let's do this project today.
Yes, I'm going to do it.
Let's call it a fun, no-holds-barred survey talk.
Yay!
Yes. Before the talk, we will take a questionnaire to decide what we will talk about. That is the questionnaire talk.
Yes.
Today, I made a mistake in the survey talk, not a survey talk. That's no good.
It happened twice today, twice.
That's right.
Before giving a talk, I take a questionnaire and decide what I am going to talk about. That is a survey talk.
Yes.
What is this talk about?
The topic this time is like this.
Then, please read them out.
First of all, number one, the painful 2023 of the Ebichu family.
And second, Musha Shugyo Free Live.
Third, Mr. Versatu New School Leaders of Taiban.
Number 4, GO TO OSAKA GIRLS CASTLE.
Number 5, what I want to say to the members at this time.
No.6, NARUKONO-chan.
No.7, The mystery of the salad Riko was eating.
Mystery?
Yes. That's it.
Now, everyone, please tell us which topic you would like to talk about.
Please do so.
Then let's vote. That's what this is for, isn't it? Okay, let's go.
I wonder what it is. Please use the voting function and throw it in, everyone. We've had a lot of gigs recently.
We had a lot of gigs, didn't we?
Everyone is throwing in their votes. What is 7?
There are a lot of one's. Five, four, three, two, one.
That's it. What's the result? Which story do you want to hear the most?
Number 6.
I see, Nonaka.I see, Nonaka.
This is, as written, a story about Nonaka.
Nonaka is a very serious girl, as everyone says.
It was during one of our lessons, when we were all together, there was something that Nonaka didn't understand.
He suddenly understood and said, "I see," in a very excited tone.
All three of us were on the same page, and it was so much fun that it wasn't the only thing we did that day.
It was too much fun, and that was not the only thing that happened that day.
During the rehearsal for the franchise event, he made a big mistake in the position of the Bang Bang beat.
I said in a high voice, "I'm so sorry," and when I said it, I probably didn't understand the meaning of the word.
It happens sometimes. Other times, I would get excited by myself.
Sometimes I mumble something by myself.
It's very funny, and everyone teases me about it.
Kaho-chan loves it so much that she is sometimes called Nonaka-chan.
That's what we call her now.
It was really cute. I see!
It's not like this.
With this beautiful voice of Nonaka, I see!
Riko made me laugh so hard.
It was really funny.
I think it's fun because this happens often.
It often happens when I have a long lesson and get confused.
I may come up with different words again.
I call them Nonaka's quotes.
I was just saying that I hope I will be able to meet new ones.
Okay, let's go to the next one. Well, let's go to the next one.
Shall we go next?
Let's vote again for the others.
Which one do you want to go to?
Let's go!
Okay.
I guess we can have the same one.
Last time, my story was chosen three times and I had nothing more to say.
This time.
This time I have prepared something for you.
Really?
You have come three times, indeed.
Okay, five, four, three, two, one.
Yes, sir.
What is it?
What's too many?
What's that?
Number 7!
This is the mystery of the salad my Riko was eating.
I haven't told this to anyone yet.
What?
What? I'm curious.
When we had the lesson before, were you the first one to eat the salad?
When I came in, she was eating a salad.
She put it in a Tupperware.
I don't know if she made it herself or not, but she was eating it.
I don't know much about your personal life, so I felt like I was getting a glimpse of your private life, which made me very happy.
I took a closer look at the ingredients of the salad, and I noticed that there were things like purple onions, and the stems were yellowish green.
I looked at the ingredients of the salad carefully, and found that there were some that looked like purple onions, some that looked like broccoli with yellowish green stems and white leaves, and some that I had never seen before.
I've never seen anything like it.
I thought, "Rico, are you okay? I want to ask you about this mystery.
What do you mean?
During that period, Ayaka and I were featured in "Anne" which was released yesterday.
We were fasting the day before the shoot or something.
I see.
Fasting is not a diet where you don't eat.
I was fasting while eating. I ate soup in the morning and at night.
I made a salad with the vegetables that were sent to me for lunch.
So, since they are vegetables that were sent to me, they are kind of fancy vegetables.
I see.
Like white ones, like cauliflower, or beets?
Beets? Not beets. Pinkish vegetable?
I don't know what it's called, but it's really good.
They're really good, but they're really good.
I put it in a Tupperware, and I'm eating it, and I'm going to the lesson early.
It's very hard, that green vegetable.
It was so hard that my jaw got tired.
When I got home, I found out that I had to boil them.
I went home and looked it up, and it turns out I had to boil it, and I had to cook it properly.
I really felt like a wild animal.
I felt like a wild animal. I thought they were eating with a really grim face.
I thought it was hard, very hard.
I thought, "Is this really edible? It was my mistake.
You have to boil it properly.
So that's what it was.
That's good. I'm glad.
The first time I saw it, I thought it was only lettuce and carrots.
I thought they put lettuce or carrots or something in it.
I was so surprised to see a very fashionable one in an ordinary Tupperware container.
I was really surprised.
It's delicious, isn't it?
Next time, please put it in and eat it.
I will.
Yes, I will. So.
You've been wondering about it.
I've been wondering about it for a long time.
Yes. Okay, let's continue.
One more survey, please.
Okay, Nonaka, you want to push?
Start!
Oh, I made a mistake.
What do you want to ask?
I'm also interested in what you want to say to the members at this time.
If this is chosen, and if number 5 is chosen, please speak one at a time.
I'm curious about what you want to say to the members at this time.
Actually, I was thinking this.
I'd like you to be more firm.I'd like it to be more solid.
Five, four, three, two, one.
What was chosen?
What do you think?
You chose well. Gentle.
You have successfully guided us.
So, I would like to say something to the members at this time.
I'll go first.
I wonder.
I've been thinking about it for a while, but I just came up with something, so I'll say it now.
Riko and I often share the same radio time.
Riko and I often do the same thing on the radio, and at such times, Riko would say, "The morning chime has rung.
Riko says "Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku no Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku" a little earlier than the rest of the time.
The middle part of the song gets a little faster.
So it was difficult to match.
That's why it's difficult to match.
One more time, a little bit. I'm conscious of it now.
I'll be conscious of it. But I'll go.
Then I'll go. Self-introductions.
The morning chime has sounded.
We're Ebisu Chugaku.
Was that normal?
Did I make you conscious?
It's okay.
How do you always feel?
Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku is a little faster.
Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku's.
They're probably in a hurry.
If I had my sister members, they would do it for me.
That's why I think I'm in a hurry.
So it's unconscious.
I've been told. Rikutan, you're not smooth.
What's with that? What is it? What is it?
It's just something I thought about.
It's Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku.
Rittan is Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku.
I guess it's like that.
That's how it is.
I was aware of it, so now it's done.
That's right.
I became a member of Riko's group.
A little conscious.
Please do.
Well then, I think I'll go do this.
A few days ago, I was sent to a regional area to work for Ebisu Chugaku, and I stayed there for a few days.
At that time, I was assigned to a room with my sister, Rika-chan, Mirei-chan, and Ayaka-chan all by themselves, and Rika-chan, Mirei-chan, and Ayaka-chan all by themselves.
Rika-chan, Mirei-chan, Kahoriko, Kokoyu-no-no-noko, and Emayuna.
But we would all get together.
I think there were five of my younger sisters in the group.
When I and Ho-chan were about to go to bed at around 1:00 a.m., it suddenly looked like a cottage from the floor below.
There was still nothing around, but I suddenly heard Nonaka's voice.
I was so surprised.
I was surprised to hear Nonaka's voice.
How many hours of sleep did I get that day?
I woke up early that morning.
I woke up at 5:30 or something.
But I went to bed right after we split up.
I slept about 4 hours.
But Yuno and Kokona seemed to have a lot of girl talk going on.
I think I stayed up until after 2:00am.
That means I only slept for about 2 or 3 hours.
Surprised, Kaho and I were about to fall asleep when we heard Nonaka's clear voice from downstairs.
He said, "You are young, aren't you?
Everyone was probably having a good time at that time. It was a midnight halt.
But I have the highest voice, so it went right through.
So my voice went through.
They could hear me very well.
So, I have a complaint. I had a complaint at that time.
Yuno-san had a complaint.
What is it?
Or what are you going to do now? Do you want to vote again?
I will.
If you want to hear this story, please vote for number 5.
Okay, bye.
I'm directing you to number 5.
I'll be sad if you don't pick number 5.
We're all 5.
I only have orange, but it's almost all of them.
I'd love to hear 2.
We'll have time for number 5.
Don't worry. We'll talk about all kinds of things.
Number 5.
That's right.
All right, then.
Five, four, three, two, one.
What was chosen?
What is it? - Yes.
Yes, number 5.
Okay, Mr. Moroko, go ahead.
I have a great claim. To all of you.
There were five of us, and at first I couldn't tell if I was supposed to say five or not.
I couldn't tell you the number of rooms, so I was assigned to one room.
I asked the manager about it, and he said that if there were five of us, we could swap rooms.
I asked the manager about it, and he told me that if I was one of the five, I could swap rooms with him.
So, since we wanted to get to know our former friends better, we decided to swap rooms.
I ended up in the same room with Yuna, just the two of us.
And that was Emma from the other Kokoyu.
Yuna and I are both pretty quiet people, so...
That's true.
We were doing a lot of things in the room.We were doing a lot of things in the room.
When I left the room, Yuna was probably the center of the group.
When I opened the door, she was gone.
What?
I was scared for a moment.
I thought, "Wait, wait.
Then, after that, when I was drying my hair in the bath.
I was drying my hair, and it was coming through the window.
Scary.
I thought it was Yusan, but then I heard it and thought, "Oh, wait, wait.
I thought it was Yuna, so I asked her about it, and it turned out to be Yuna.
It was indeed Yuzan, and she made an amazing complaint.
That's scary.
I was afraid of that.
Yuna.
But there was a kindness.
After I repeatedly ping-ponged and opened the door several times, at the end of the session.
I would leave a cup of tea for them. Outside.
No, I don't need that kindness.
What is that, like a tea shop?
It's just so amazing, I don't know what it is.
Tea?
Oh, no.
I don't know what it is.
I don't really know, but he left it for me.
I took it gratefully. I took it gratefully.
Why didn't you just say, "Here you go"?
Yes, you went to all the trouble of ping-ponging and leaving it there.
I don't know why I did that.
I'm glad you had a good time.
I'm glad.
Yes, I am. That was the story.
That was the story. Well, let's go one more time.
Okay, then.
Let's go to the survey.
Vote
I would like to hear number 2.
Number 2
I wish I could hear number 2.
Oh, but I think it's all over the place.
Oh, there are a lot of number 2s. It's nice.
Oh, there's one.
There's a lot of number 5, too.
Number 2.
Lots of orange and blue.
Number 5 and number 2, I think.
Number 5?
I'm getting a lot of things I'd like to be a member of at this time.
All right, we'll see you by the deadline in five, four, three, two, one.
Bye-bye.
The result is...
Number 2!
Let's see, it's the warrior training program Freia.
Let's see, what is it, where to start?
I guess I'll start with Kobe on February 4.
First of all, what is a warrior training?
This is a group of, let's see, 10 members of EBICHU.
There are five of us, including myself, who are called the younger members.
The five of us are planning to perform live by ourselves without the help of the older members.
So now we are doing live shows with just the five of us.
We started on February 4 in Kobe.
We have just finished two shows.
But we had to come up with the live show, the set and the MC by ourselves.
COCONA plays a central role in coming up with these ideas.
We would say what songs we wanted to play, and COCONA would put them all together.
COCONA put it all together and did the formations and dances for about one song.
Why do I have to write the MC script? Mine always comes up with the MC script.
I thought I'd give it a try.
After I did it, the principal was thinking about it too.
After I sent it, the principal's guy came to me.
After I sent it, the principal came to me and asked me what I should do, and in the end COCONA put it all together.
So I thought it would be difficult.
It was the first time we had a face-to-face meeting.
Not online, but in person.
It was a lot of fun.
The farewell party and the "Notification sound" session? I did that.
I was really impressed with the way he was like.
Online, you can only see so much.
Sometimes there are people who are standing up.
So some of them looked like this when they saw the whole body.
I also had a lot of people wearing the same outfit as mine.
I was so happy to see people wearing the same clothes as mine.
I was really happy, and some of them even made my clothes for me.
It made me really happy.
It was a lot of fun.
Three more shows?
Three more performances.
We're putting in some difficult songs here, too.
I can't say much about it.
So I'm going to do my best.
How do you like playing live with five members?
How do you feel about performing as a five-piece?
Well...
Yes. Live performance.
But we don't have any older sisters.
I can't make mistakes.
So it's even harder to make mistakes than usual.
So I feel like they are really into it.
Also, the rehearsal is like an open rehearsal.
It's like a real rehearsal.I've already done it there like it was the real thing.
I'm so tired.
I always regret that.
I'm going to fix it before the next show.
Do you give feedback after the show?
Not that I make time for it.
I don't make time for it.
This song was too fast...
We talk a little bit.
Thank you very much.
I've got a show in two days.
The next one is on the 10th.
So please come.
Please, come.
Please come and see your five little sisters.
Please.
One more thing.
One more.
That's the last one.
Which story would you like to hear? I'll put it to a vote.
What do you think? What would you like to hear?
What do you want to hear?
What would you like to hear?
I can't hear number one and number three.
Number 1 and 3 and 4?
Oh, and number four.
Oh, and number 4.
Okay, we'll see you by the deadline.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Poof!
What is it?
Ah!
What's number 5?
Number 5...
I'm gonna get killed...
Number 4, what I want to say!
What? !
Well... you know...
You're right, this is the first time in all my years of doing these surveys that I've gotten the same one 3 times.
It's so hard! What do you want to say? Well, I'll tell you what I want to say...
I'd like to tell you that I'm a very bad sleeper, so I'm going to go on an expedition.
Sleeping? When I went to stay at my cousin's house, he let me sleep in the same bed with him because I was tiny.
I was kicking him so hard that he said he didn't want to sleep with me anymore.
What is it about New Year's? He went to the trouble of taking the futon off the bed and waking me up, saying he did it, and that he was scared! I don't know... I don't remember.
I don't know, I don't remember it at all... so I told her that if she ever happens to be in the same room with me, she should try to sleep.
Isn't that too funny? He wakes up like this and says he did it... and then wakes up all the way back to sleep... and then wakes up all the way back to sleep.
That's funny! I'll send you a video if it's interesting. I'll do it!
It's so funny!
Okay, Baby 2, before Corona.
Before Corona, we used to eat together in the lesson room, but recently...
But recently, since the rehearsal for the FC event, when we were eating together in the room, we were all sitting at different tables, and there were 10 of us.
Rika-chan was the one who talked, and since Mirei couldn't speak at that time, Rika-chan did most of the talking while Kahoniko said something to the other.
So there were 10 of us, but only 3 of us were talking.
So there were 10 people in the room, but only 3 of us were talking. You know what I mean? It's hard to get in, right?
Yes, I'm quite nervous between rehearsals and the next rehearsal, and I have to eat.
I didn't go in because I had to eat. I didn't realize it at the time, but Rika-chan talked all the time.
Kaho is also very kind, so she's always saying things to me, like, "I'm listening too.
And out of 10 people in the group, only 2 of them talk.
Yoon-ho and I talk to each other sometimes.
I see what you mean.
That's it! There! If it's quiet, he'll be like, "I see...
I'd like to try it. He's definitely not talking.
Rika said it herself, but I'm the only one talking.
I'm sorry! I'll try my best! I see. I see! I'll be waiting for you.
Well then, that's all! That's all for now!
Was it weird? It was a survey talk!
Well then, since February is the month of Valentine's Day, we'd like to do something that Obituaries rarely do, and that is a very exciting project!
Let's call it! A funny and funny Valentine's Day!
Here are the rules! From now on, we're going to play a game where the two of us have to make a cliche of our own confession lines that will make the other person want to say "ok" to us.
(Of course, if the dialogue isn't working, or if the other person doesn't want to ok the line, you're out.
If you are out, you will be punished with a quick game. What's "Saku-kutto"?
What's "Saku-kutto"?
It's great... if we both do it together, it'll come right back to you! More and more...
Let's change to the Valentine poi BGM.
I love this song by Ebichu...
What else? Valentine poi?
Cute and cute... Oh, are you sure there's something else?
Valentine poi song... from Ebichu...
I don't know.
"Kyuroun"?
Kuruun?
A little stylish
Stylish.
I'm getting encores.
There's a lot of encores.
So many encores. We got a lot of encores.
I got a lot of encores.
Please choose a few from this list.
Oh, no...
Temptation is cute. Indeed.
Sure, sure.
You don't want to pick one of my favorites?
It's good.
I like the pimple.
Oh, it's cute.Oh, it's so cute.
Oh, I ate too much chocolate.
I got a pimple.
It looks like you have a pimple.
Yes, I have.
Oh, that's not good.
I really don't do confession lines like this.
I'll get around to it.
I'll start with a finesse.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Okay.
Let's start with the winner. The winner.
If it's the loser, it feels a little bit like a penalty game, which I don't like.
Let's start with the winner.
First, let's play rock-paper-scissors-scissors. Encore.
What should I do first?
I'll start with the one I like the best in the morning.
Let's go from the first thing, let's go from the first thing, let's go from the first thing, let's go from the first thing, let's go from the first thing, let's go from the first thing
I'm a confession jelly, that's right, don't make me research you, not my friend!
I'm not your friend!
That's not a vowel sound. That's not a vowel game.
It's a ta-ta. Yes.
I love you so much.
I want to spend the night with you. I'm scared.
Wait a minute, ouch, ouch, fly away!
Confession! Confession!
It's a quick "butsudan" beam!
I'm not here! I'm here, I'm here, I'm here, I'm here.
I'll always be with you.
Hey, you're getting pimples.
Can I see you after midnight? You're so cute.
Lulu, the beauty queen?
I'm so happy to be with you.
You want to do this project? I'm sure five more will come around soon.
It's so difficult.
I'll rally for 10 more minutes.
I thought it was an adult's confession.
Tomi.
Tomi, Kyoo...
Wanna go to Tokyo Station with me?
What's there? What's in Tokyo Station?
What's in Tokyo Station?
There are a lot of things.
Sopping Mall, for example.
Can we go?
Can we go again?
Sure.
But we tend to end up together.
Like "yo" and "ne".
Meaning.
I like you so much that I don't know what it means.
I like you again.
Ki, ki, ki, ki.
Ki?
You look like you're glowing yellow.
Kagayaki, it's soooooooooooo cool.
Ru, ru, ru, ru, ru, ru, ru, ru, ru, ru, ru, ru, ru, ru, ru, ru, ru, ru
Looks great
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh
Uh-uh.
I'm so glad I get to spend time with you.
Not you! Make it me!
Rival, rival! I'm your idol.
Look me in the eye!
It's my hand again.
Ehhhh...
No!
No! Say "I love you" one more time!
Hands? Your hand?
Can I hold your hand? Oh?
Don't think about it, Kasami. Yes, it's okay. Can I hold your hand?
What?
I get sick to my stomach. Being with you.
It's too different with you, isn't it?
I was told no.
No, it's not. My stomach goes crazy. It's a good thing.
Too much fun, too much laughter, too much stomach overtaking, it's okay now.
Like, it's so funny, it hurts.
Like a stress disease.
I think you should break up with them immediately. That's the kind of person I'm talking about.
So, what do you want to do?
What's the punishment?
Oh, no. Punishment.
That's a rare one.
I'll say it, it's like a game of punishment.
Blink for 20 seconds.
I'm sorry. What happens if I blink? What happens if I blink, do I have to blink for 40 seconds?
One time.
Can I start?
No. It's dry today.
All right, here we go.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
That's good. That's good. Looking good. That's good.
Twenty. Oh!
I got it!
It's good.
It's not too dull.
It's good. I got it.
If I make a mistake this time, it's going to get longer and longer.This one feels like it will grow and grow if I make a mistake this time.
Another.
Oh, another. I see.
It's amazing how it keeps growing.
What did I just do?
Being with you. Oh, okay.
It's good. I like it.
I want it.
You're cute already?
It's cute like a dog!
I want to be with you forever!
Don't go away, stay with me.
I should've chosen "love".
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Call me "love.
No, you're cute.
Hey, Tor.
To.
Tor.
TOE
toe
Like a tomato
Your cheeks are so cute.
They're cute! They're tomatoes! They're bright red!
You're so cute! Hey!
Hey.
Let's call each other till we fall asleep.
Hmm?
Hmm? Are you kidding me?
Are you kidding me?
Why are you saying that when you're so cute?
What? Why?
I don't know.
Uu?
It's the salt.
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh...
I want to be surrounded by your kindness as wide as the sea.
Oh, wow. You're like that a lot.
Like a lot. It's a lot. A little.
It's embarrassing.
It's a lot. I'm sorry.
Well, what is it? It's nice.
Good.
How long are you gonna make me wait?
Why?
I saw it in the comments earlier, but I've read too many shoujo manga to remember it.
Maybe I remember the royal kyun-kyun. So that's how it is.
No?
I've loved you ever since you gave me the throat rain.
Dokudoku!
Boom, boom, boom!
Which one was it again?
The one with the "ta" in it.
Ta.
I love it!
I love you!
From now on, we'll be lovers, not friends! I love you!
I'm looking forward to it!
Why? Why?
You're not a funny guy.
I see... I see... I'm no good.
Yo!
If you like!
If you like! If you like! If you want! Will you go out with me?
Oh!
It's the high road!
Ka!
All you get is a bowl of seafood. Wait a minute.
You can go there! You can go from Kaisendon!
You can go from kaisendon!
Ka, ka, ka, ka...
Kaisendon! Kaisendon!
Ka, ka, ka, ka, ka, kan, kan, kou!
Kankoku?
Kankou!
Oh! Punishment game!
Yes! Oh! Punishment game: blink for 20 seconds.
I'm starting to cry. Well then, I'll still have to prohibit you from blinking for 20 seconds.
Let's start!
Oh no, I don't have good eyesight.
6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20 !
Oh! I'm crying, I'm crying!
Oh no, I forgot I have weak eyes.
I'm always crying when we shoot.
Yes, I'm crying.
But I was able to hold it in.
I was able to hold back. That's great.
Okay, so, let's start.So, I'll just say, "KARA.
Ka? Riko.
I'm already on the line, so I'm only on the line.
KA, I love you, you cute, cute, cute.
Yo yo yo yo!
Yo!
Say I love you four times.
He's so cute.
what is it?
hand
Hands.
Your hands are open.
Can't you connect them?
Oh, my God.
That's so cute.
Cute.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
Ew.
No, no, no, no.
Let's get some ink.
When you live with us.
Ooh.
La-la-la... then we'll buy a camel... and then we'll live together.
We'll buy a camel and live together. Oh, my God, it's coming in a second.
La-la. Okay.
Okay, so, if we buy a camel, we'll live together.
That's what I meant.
I'll buy a sea otter and live with him.
If you want to cry, let's live together.
Yo, yo, yo?
Yes.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
I wish you'd just sit with me.
Oh, I'm scared.
Nah, nah, nah, nah.
What are you talking about? You love me so much.
Cute.
Ni.
2. 2.
Meow.
Cat. Cat.
Oh no, it's 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
I can't answer.
The second Bastin game.
I'm told I blink too much.
It's hard.
What is it? The next Bustin' Game.
What would you have said if it was 2?
Wink left and right.
Can you do it?
Which one?
Hmm? This way?
Oh, it's done... but that's it...
I hope we can do this again, maybe with just the two of us, or maybe with just the four of us.
Again! Which cupturner? Which Cup Turner?
When we're together... we'll have them do it... and it'll be a limited project for February...
Who's good at this? Cocona and Mirei.
Next February, let's have Cocona and Mirei do it together. Let's make the game a little more difficult.
Let's have a penalty game with those two!
The members for next February have been decided! Keep it in mind!
Well then, that's all for now, here's a happy and fluffy Valentine's Day!
This is the 54th episode of the showroom of the shrimpers, and it's coming to an end in no time at all.
The final ranking. I haven't announced the ranking yet. I'm sure. The final ranking.
We are in fifth place, starting from fifth place, Kasabut-san. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you. Third place, Mr. Shackelford. Thank you very much.
Second place, Ms. Koyuki. Thank you very much. First place, Ms. Montt. Thank you very much.
Yes, it was fun, wasn't it?
It was my first time, so it was fun. Nonaka: Your confession is very strong. I guess it's because of the manga expression.
If so, I guess that means Kaho-chan is strong too. I read a lot of Kaho-chan manga. That's for sure. Kaho-chan seems to have a lot of paintings.
Yes, she seems to be for hardship. I can't think of any. I'd like you to try it. Between the strong Cocona and Mirei, Kaho's.
Let's have them try it. Next February, I'd like you three to do it.
Shall we announce it then? Yes, I'll do that.
Where was it? As I mentioned earlier, the Musha Shugyo Free Live & Benefit Event is going on right now, and the next one will be held on Saturday, February 25th, two days from now at the San Parada Stage on the first basement floor of Kenal City Hakata in Fukuoka.
The next event will be held on Saturday, February 25th at the Samparada Stage in the basement of Kenal City Hakata in Fukuoka. Please come and join us. Please come and visit us.
And JoJo John.
The Spring Tour 2023 100% EBISM will be held on Saturday, April 15, at the Mori no Hall 21 in Chiba Prefecture.
Yes.
21?
21.
21. from the main hall will tour 16 cities and 17 parks throughout Japan.
Yes. 21. 21.
Please check the official website for details. Please check the official website for details.
You are really going all over the country, aren't you?
That's right.
We are going to Okinawa this time, too.
We didn't have Okinawa last spring, did we?
That's right. There was no Okinawa.Yes, there wasn't. There wasn't one.
I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it.
Please look forward to it.
I'm counting on you.
Yes, please. So, this is the end of the 54th episode of EBICHU's Delightful and FUFUNA Showroom.
Yes.
We will let you know about the next episode as soon as it is decided.
This show will also include the review meeting that will take place after the show, so please be sure to check it out.
Yes, I'm going to end the transmission for a moment.
We will resume in a little while, so please stay tuned.
Thank you very much.
Yes.
If you have anything you want to tell us at the review meeting, please leave a comment.
That's all for now.
Sumiken Mistuak.
Bye bye.
Next time notice
Thank you for your hard work.
Well then, to Mr. Nakayama, it's been a while since we last met.
It's been a while, hasn't it? How long has it been?
It's been about 5 months.
That's right. The last time was with Ayaka and Kaho.
That's right, it was in October.
Wow.
We did that at that time, too. The survey talk.
That was it then.
That episode was so interesting that Survey Talk has become a regular feature.
I see.
I've been on the show quite a bit, and I always think about what I'm going to say in the "Questionnaire Talk.
There is always a column for what Nonaka wants to talk about.
And the fans choose what they want to talk about. So I think about it every time.
The number of people who come to the showroom has increased, so it seems that some people don't get a turn at the showroom.
Mr. Nonaka, have you been on the show for three months in a row?
It seems like every month.
MC Isn't that it? Isn't this the month of reinforcement?
Is that what you mean?
But I've been on about 3 months in a row, and I've never MC'd once.
So you'll be MC next month.
That's right. Up until now, it was pretty much the lower grade students, so we decided at 9 o'clock.
But they don't get chosen every time. It's usually "YUNO.
Is it bad luck or do you know everyone?
I don't know if it's bad luck or if everyone knows it, but it's usually YUNO that gets the MC.
It's not about Mr. Nakayama, but it is said that the program is more stable if the non-MC is good.
That is true.
It was good.
How was your first showroom in a while? Mr. Nakayama.
Well, I guess there are two of us now.
I don't know.
If the showroom is not well received, we may go back to three people.
It might be just a coincidence.
If it had been three times next time, it would have been a bit of a disaster.
It would have been different.
But it was fun even with two people.
It was fun. We talked quite often, so we talked a lot about clothes.
Yes, we did. You are very good at it, Mr. Nakayama.
What is?
It's written down.
Thank you very much.
But he said you two are good. They don't have a bad reputation. Straw, straw. It's not bad.
I was so squeamish I didn't have a heart.
That was good.
It was good. I said something like, "Sometimes I get on the wrong line.
I was in a hurry. I said all kinds of things.
You should open that drawer at least once in a series.
That's right.
If you don't take it down to the bottom of the shelf, you won't do it.
They really don't do that. This is the kind of "kyun kyu-kyu" type.
I have an image that you often do confession lines in the newspaper book.
That's true.
But, you know, there were a lot of similar lines.
That's for sure.
Even though it was pointed out to me.
There's a lot of this kind of thing.
You don't notice the book you're saying it in.
That's for sure.
I was feeling a bit gutted and my soul was drained.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Come back to me, my soul.
I'm scared, scared.
Rakuko or Rakuko?
Was there a lot of "ra"?
Yes, there were a lot of "ra" and "rakuko". And there were also a lot of Yo.
There was a lot of Yo.
Well, well, well.
I'm glad you were pleased with the show.
It was good.
About once a year.
So, Mr. Nakano, please close the meeting on a good note.
Close it on a good note?
Let's end it with a "kyun-kyun".
Why? You want to close with "Kyunkyun"?
Thank you for today.
It's been a while since I've been in a showroom, but I had a great time. Thanks to you.
I'll see you next month.
See you again?
See you again.See you again.
So long, bye-bye.
Bye bye. You were cute.
I see.